March 4th, 2022. 3:00 AM. Park City, Utah.
Kouri Richins places a frantic 911 call. Her husband, Eric, is unresponsive in their bed. Paramedics arrive within minutes.
It's too late.
Eric Richins, 39 years old, father of three, is pronounced dead at the scene.
The cause of death?  Fentanyl poisoning.  Five times the lethal dose.
But this wasn't an accidental overdose. Eric didn't use drugs.  He was murdered.
And the person who killed him?  The woman who called 911.  His wife.
This is Mind Crimes.
Today, we're examining one of the most disturbing cases of 2026. A case that combines financial desperation, narcissistic manipulation, and the weaponization of grief itself.
Kouri Richins. A Utah mother of three. Real estate investor. And, as of March 16th, 2026,  a convicted murderer.
But before we get to the murder, we need to understand who Kouri and Eric Richins were, and how their seemingly perfect life was built on a foundation of lies.
Kouri and Eric Richins met in their twenties and married in 2013. They settled in the affluent ski town of Park City, Utah, a place known for its mountain views, luxury homes, and the Sundance Film Festival.
Eric came from a successful family. His parents owned a masonry business, and Eric himself was a skilled stone mason. He was described by friends as hardworking, loyal, and devoted to his three sons.
Kouri, on the other hand, was ambitious. She started a real estate business flipping houses. Buying properties, renovating them, and selling for profit. On social media, she portrayed herself as a successful businesswoman living the American dream.
But the reality  was far different.
Court documents revealed that Kouri's real estate empire was collapsing. Her business was losing money. By 2022, she was in debt to the tune of seven point five million dollars.
A forensic accountant who testified at trial described her finances as "imploding." Her net worth the day after Eric's death?  Negative one point six million.
But Eric didn't know the full extent of the problem. Kouri kept him in the dark about the mounting debts, failed investments, and financial chaos.
What Eric did know was this:  he didn't trust his wife.
By early 2022, Eric Richins was becoming suspicious. He noticed irregularities in their finances. He questioned Kouri's spending. And he began taking steps to protect himself.
In February 2022, Eric changed his will. He removed Kouri as a beneficiary, placing his assets into a trust for his three sons. He also confided in friends that his marriage was struggling.
But Kouri had other plans.  Plans that involved fentanyl.
February 14th, 2022. Valentine's Day.
Kouri and Eric go out to dinner. According to court testimony, Kouri had recently acquired hydrocodone pills from an acquaintance, a housekeeper named Carmen Lauber, who lived at a sober living facility.
But hydrocodone wasn't strong enough. Kouri wanted something more lethal. She specifically requested  "some of the Michael Jackson" stuff. A reference to fentanyl, the drug that killed the pop star.
After Valentine's dinner, Eric became violently ill. He told friends he believed his wife had tried to poison him. He even said the words out loud:  "Kouri is trying to kill me."
But he didn't go to the police.  And he didn't leave.
Two weeks after the Valentine's Day incident, Kouri went back to Carmen Lauber. This time, she got what she wanted:  fentanyl pills.
Text messages recovered by investigators show Kouri picking up the drugs on February 26th, 2022.  Six days later,  Eric was dead.
On the night of March 4th, Kouri and Eric celebrated closing a real estate deal. Kouri mixed Eric a Moscow Mule, a cocktail made with vodka, ginger beer, and lime juice.
She brought it to him in bed.
Eric drank it.  And within hours,  he was dead.
Medical examiners found five times the lethal dose of fentanyl in his system. The amount, prosecutors later argued, showed that Kouri Richins wanted Eric  "not only dead, but good and dead."
Most people who commit murder try to lay low.  Not Kouri Richins.
In March 2023, one year after her husband's death, Kouri self-published a children's book titled "Are You with Me?" The book was marketed as a way to help children cope with grief after losing a parent.
Kouri appeared on local TV, smiling and promoting the book. She talked about how much she missed Eric. She described their marriage as loving and supportive.
It was a masterclass in narcissistic manipulation.  And it made investigators even more suspicious.
Behind the scenes, detectives were building a case.
They interviewed Carmen Lauber, the woman who sold Kouri the fentanyl. They analyzed Kouri's phone records. They dug into her finances. The seven point five million dollar debt. The collapsing real estate business. The one point four million dollar life insurance policy on Eric's life.
And they uncovered something else:  Kouri had been having an affair.
Testimony at trial revealed that Kouri had been involved with another man during her marriage. Prosecutors argued she wanted to leave Eric, but she didn't want to leave his money.
As Chief Prosecutor Brad Bloodworth put it:  "She wanted to leave Eric Richins, but she did not want to leave his money."
The motive was clear:  financial desperation, plus affair, plus life insurance,  equals murder.
On May 8th, 2023, Kouri Richins was arrested and charged with aggravated murder.
The trial began in February 2026, nearly four years after Eric's death.
Prosecutors presented a mountain of evidence. Text messages between Kouri and Carmen Lauber discussing drug purchases. Testimony from Eric's friends, who said he believed Kouri was trying to poison him. Financial records showing Kouri's seven point five million dollar debt. Cell phone data placing Kouri at the drug pickup location. Forensic evidence showing five times the lethal dose of fentanyl in Eric's system. Testimony from the man Kouri was having an affair with.
The defense argued that Eric could have overdosed accidentally, that the drug dealer was unreliable, and that the prosecution's case was circumstantial.
But the jury wasn't convinced.
On March 16th, 2026, after just over three hours of deliberation, the jury returned a verdict:
Guilty of aggravated murder.
Guilty of attempted aggravated murder.
Guilty of forgery and insurance fraud.
Kouri Richins showed no emotion as the verdict was read.
She faces life in prison without parole.
The Kouri Richins case is a textbook example of narcissistic manipulation.
She constructed a public persona of the grieving widow. She wrote a children's book about loss. She appeared on television talking about how much she loved her husband.
All while knowing she had poisoned him with a lethal dose of fentanyl.
Psychologists who study cases like this point to a pattern: narcissists don't just commit crimes,  they perform them. They need the world to see them as victims, as heroes, as martyrs. The grief book wasn't just a cover story.  It was part of the performance.
But in the end, the performance fell apart. The text messages, the financial records, the testimony from people who saw through the facade,  it all added up.
Three children are now without both parents. Eric is dead. And Kouri will spend the rest of her life in prison.
This case reminds us that the most dangerous people aren't always the ones who look dangerous.  Sometimes,  they're the ones who look perfect.
Thank you for watching Mind Crimes. If you found this case as disturbing as I did, please subscribe and share this video. And if you have suggestions for future cases, leave a comment below.
Until next time.